[{"answer": "No.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "And when it came to the actual moment of capture and arrest, did you actually see that happening?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "It's been a horrendous week because in many different ways, all of us have experienced the horror of the bombing.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "How are you feeling now it's all over?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "You know, we don't know much about the injuries, Piers.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "Elizabeth, what do we know about the injuries he may have sustained?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "Can you hear me, Susan?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "I think we were all just really on edge, really nervous about what was going to happen next.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "What was that like?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "It was terrifying.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "What did you think about, learning that he was living here or at least hiding out here during the last 24 hours?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "Oh, geez.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "How does Boston come back?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Well, it's been a harrowing time for us and I'm sure for the victims' families and friends who have been spending a long week wondering where he's at.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "What would you like to see?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "Was it?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "There probably will.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Let me ask you about that, Juliette Kayyem, because that could be a big question mark once the celebration of this particular operation which has clearly been successful, once that dies down, there will be an inquest into what has gone on in the background to all this, and it has turned out the FBI did indeed interview one of these two brothers two years ago and he is somebody that they now believe was having quite serious Islamic fundamentalist development in his life, will there be raised eyebrows about this?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "Well, I'm feeling good.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "How are you feeling personally about the way this has all played out tonight?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Yes, it has been, by all law enforcement.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "This has been a successful operation by the FBI, hasn't it?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "There are two big questions right away.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "What is going to happen now procedurally that they've got him under arrest and have him alive?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Well, he will get a fair trial.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Alan Dershowitz, how will that play out, do you think?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "Governor?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "I just want to say very briefly -- thank you, thank you, thank you.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Mayor Menino?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Four days ago, my city was ruthlessly attacked.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Commissioner Davis?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "As the police chief of Watertown, I can't be prouder of my community and the men and women of the Watertown Police Department.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Watertown Police Chief Deveau?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Excuse me.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "Chief, did you have communication with the suspect?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "I just want to thank all those who sent their thoughts and prayers to Officer Donohue and his family.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Chief MacMillan from the MBTA?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "There was a call that came in to the Watertown police, three Boston police officers along with state troopers and FBI agents responded to Franklin Street.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "How did the events transpire at the boat?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "We always want to take all the suspects alive.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Can you talk about the imperative of taking him alive?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "We always want to take somebody alive so we can find out what happened, why it happened, and we can hold them for justice.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Can you talk about why you wanted to take him?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Actually, I don't have that information.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Have they aided and abetted the suspect?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "I think based upon our investigation at this point in time, the citizens of the city of Boston and this area can be confident that the threat has been removed.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "This is it?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "Suspect is in serious condition at the hospital.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "What kind of condition is the suspect in?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "The suspects came to our attention after a vicious assassination of a police officer at MIT and a subsequent robbery that occurred where we got videotape from a gas station.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "They didn't rob the 7-Eleven so how did you know they were there at the same time?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "The man who found him at the boat said that he was covered with blood.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Was he shot by police officer?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "My assessment of that particular incident is that he was assassinated in his cruiser.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "What do you know about that?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "He was responding to a call for a disturbance.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "Do you know what he was doing there?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "We certainly did not give an all-clear.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "Could they have been at risk?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "There's no report of explosives with him at capture but I got to tell you, I was at the scene last night just after this incident occurred.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Did he have explosives with him when he was captured?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "Actually, the United States attorney may -- the FBI may want to explain that.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "Could you explain that for us?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "There was no Miranda warning given, they were claiming a public safety exception.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "What was the question?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "There is a public safety exemption in cases of national security and potential charges involving acts of terrorism.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "Could we get an explanation?", "qSentId": 608}, {"answer": "You know, what I indicated earlier is that this is still an active, an ongoing investigation.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "Will you seek the federal death penalty?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "Straight to the boat and then can or the colonel talk a little about what happened when you were on the scene.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Karen?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "Yes, it was outside the perimeter during the day.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "Was the boat searched during the day on the perimeter?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "Is there a chance the suspect won't make it?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "Was supposed to speak already 15 minutes ago.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 710, "question": "And the president, going back to Jessica Yellin -- do we know what time the president's due to speak?", "qSentId": 709}, {"answer": "Well, they're asserting that there is a public safety exception that allows them to question him and then potentially use the information -- use the statements against him.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "What did you make of what they've been saying and positioning the case from the start here?", "qSentId": 718}, {"answer": "That's not at all clear.", "docId": "130419pmt", "aSentId": 721, "question": "Are they right?", "qSentId": 720}]